{
    "id": "275c612bca844dbc8e03c349b8e7e1d2",
    "title": "Articles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Gold is ……………………….. precious metal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Honest men speak ……………………….. truth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He looks as stupid as ……………………….. owl.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to meet Brad Pit, …………………. actor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What did you do with ……………………… camera I lent you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is going out with ………………………… German girl.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He remained ………………………… bachelor all his life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘What is that noise?’ ‘I think it is ……………………….. helicopter.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited for ………………………….. hour and then I went home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She showed me …………………………. one-pound coin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}